# **Dmitry Artamonov**

# Full Stack Developer, Backend Developer

Kiryat Motzkin | 535-002162 | artamonov2009@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

As a Full Stack Developer, I possess valuable skills in Python and JavaScript programming, with a particular focus on projects with complex Backend components. My expertise also extends to API development and efficient data processing, where I have successfully automated pricing strategies and optimized product management by integrating CMS with external services. Additionally, I have honed my skills in creating chatbots for Telegram. I am constantly learning and prefer projects that challenge and develop me as a developer.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Python, OOP, Django, Django REST, Javascript, Node.js, React, HTML, CSS, PostgreSQL, Git, MS Excel

#### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

**Restobot** - <u>GitHub BE</u> | <u>GitHub FE</u> | <u>The bot</u> | <u>Admin Page</u> | (Python, Django, Django Rest, Aiogram, JavaScript, React, PostgreSQL, Amazon S3)

Facilitate communication between restaurants and their clients using a Telegram bot

- In the admin web app: edit the menu (add, edit, delete dishes, create categories), receive and approve orders
- In the bot: Access the restaurant's menu, view pictures, descriptions, and prices of dishes
- In the bot: Add dishes to the cart, edit the cart, submit the order
- Direct communication between client and restaurant through messages in Telegram

#### **Dynamic prices for marketplaces** - GitHub | (Python, OOP, API)

Changes prices of products on marketplaces to achieve maximum profit

- Utilized JSON Web Tokens and local Storage to store encrypted user information client-side.
- Get with API and JSON sales data and analyze it for each product
- Change prices on marketplace with API
- Save all changes to JSON and XLS for user convenience

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Co-Founder and CEO: ZEERO.ru

St. Petersburg, Russia | 2017 - Present

Github | LinkedIn | Portfolio

- Created successful online store from scratch
- Designed dynamic prices system (Python + API) to ensure maximum profit of sales on marketplaces
- Organized the order delivery and payment process, integrated with delivery services and payment gateways
- Implemented API connection with marketplaces
- Created data processing system to load marketplaces sales reports

Projects and Campaign Lead, Head of regional office: Greenpeace Russia St. Petersburg, Russia | 2001 - 2019

- Planned, executed, and monitored diverse sustainability and conservation initiatives in collaboration with stakeholders
- Conducted environmental impact assessments, facilitated community engagement, and secured funding for projects
- Leaded teams up to 50 employers and volunteers to achieve project's goals

#### **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Tel Aviv, Israel | 03/2023 - 08/2023

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

# Generation Python for professionals, Generation Python for advanced

Russia | 09/2022 - Present

BeeGeek School

## Radio-Electronics Engineer, BA

St. Petersburg, Russia

Saint-Petersburg University of Telecommunications

1999

## **LANGUAGES**

English - Fluent, Russian - Native